zapafly.net 2011-05-26

# Social Search Engine - Social Search Engine

Privacy Policy

## PRIVACY POLICY

## General Statement

This Privacy Policy (�Privacy Policy�) discloses the privacy practices for ZaPaFlY, LLC d/b/a ZaPaFlY with regard to your (�You� or �Your�) use of the websites (www.ZaPaFlY.com and (the �Sites�). ZaPaFlY is committed to Your privacy. The following policy applies to all of the websites owned by ZaPaFlY including ZaPaFlY.com. ZaPaFlY hereby notifies You of:

  1. What personally identifiable information of Yours is collected from You through these sites and how the information is used. 
  2. How the information may be shared. 
  3. How ZaPaFlY protects Your information. 
  4. How You can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

  1. WHAT PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION OF YOURS IS COLLECTED AND HOW THE INFORMATION IS USED.
    1. Information Collection and Use  
ZaPaFlY is the sole owner of the information collected on these sites. ZaPaFlY will not sell, share, transfer or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this Privacy Policy. ZaPaFlY collects information from You on certain pages on these sites.
    2. Registration  
On certain pages on the Sites, You will be asked for Your contact information: (such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services, educational level and interests and/or billing information). Such information allows ZaPaFlY to process and fulfill Your request. Your contact information is also used to confirm Your identity and to contact You about the services on the Sites for which You may have expressed interest. When the Sites requests Your identity, the Sites will clearly indicate the purpose of the inquiry before the information is requested.
    3. IP Addresses  
Every computer connected to the Internet is given a domain name and a set of numbers that serve as that computer's "Internet Protocol" or IP address. When You request a page from any page within the Sites, our Web servers automatically recognize Your domain name and IP address. The domain name and IP address reveal nothing personal about You other than the IP address from which You have accessed the Sites. ZaPaFlY may use IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the Sites, track Your movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use.
    4. Children�s and Minor�s Privacy  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is uniquely important, particularly on the Internet. The Sites are designed to provide commercial business information and services for adults. These sites are not designed to attract minors, in particular children under the age of 13. ZaPaFlY does not market to or knowingly collect information from anyone under the age of 13. Children should always get permission from their parents before sending any information about themselves (such as their names, email addresses, and phone numbers) to anyone over the Internet.
    5. Opt Out Procedures  
You may opt-out of receiving communications from ZaPaFlY at the point where the Sites request personally identifiable information about You. To be removed from an e-mail list, please complete an online contact us form or follow the instructions contained in any e-mail correspondence that you receive from ZaPaFlY. To unsubscribe from a third party service, you must contact that third party directly.
    6. Cookies  
A cookie is a small piece of data that is sent to Your browser from a Web server and stored on Your computer�s hard drive. A cookie cannot read data off Your hard disk or read cookie files created by other sites. Use of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on the Sites. Some ZaPaFlY Services features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. Some of ZaPaFlY�s business partners may use cookies on the Sites. However, ZaPaFlY has no access to or control over these cookies. ZaPaFlY and its business partners may use cookies to better personalize the content, banners, and/or promotions that You see on the Sites. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the setting of Your browser. You can reset your Browser to refuse all cookies or allow Your browser to show You when a cookie is being sent. If You reject the cookies on the Sites, You may still use the Sites. The only drawback to this is that You may be limited in some areas of these sites.
  2. HOW INFORMATION MAY BE SHARED.
    1. Sharing  
ZaPaFlY may share aggregated demographic information with ZaPaFlY�s partners. This is not linked to any personal information that can identify any individual person. ZaPaFlY may partner with another party to provide specific services. When You sign up for these services, ZaPaFlY will share names or other contact information that is necessary for the third party to provide these services. ZaPaFlY�s contractual arrangements with third parties with which it shares Your personal information prohibits the third parties from using that information except for the explicit purpose of providing the services for which it was provided. To the extent that Your credit card information is collected by ZaPaFlY or any of its affiliates or subsidiaries, such information will be kept in confidence and will not be shared with any third parties (other than consumer credit agencies) without Your prior consent. ZaPaFlY shall not be liable for the transfer or disclosure of any personal identification information resulting from loss or distribution of data, the delineation or corruption of storage media, power failures, natural phenomena, riots, acts of vandalism, sabotage, terrorism or any other event beyond ZaPaFlY�s control.
    2. Sale of Assets, Merger, Acquisition, Bankruptcy  
Information collected from You may be transferred to a third party as a result of a sale, merger or corporate transfer involving ZaPaFlY.
    3. Spam  
Notwithstanding anything to the contrary herein, ZaPaFlY maintains a strict �No-Spam� policy, which means that ZaPaFlY does not intend to sell, rent or otherwise give your e-mail address to a third party without Your consent.
    4. Legal Requests  
ZaPaFlY cooperates with law enforcement inquiries, as well as other third parties, to enforce laws and third party rights, such as intellectual property rights and laws relating to fraud. ZaPaFlY can (and You authorize ZaPaFlY to) disclose Your personal data and other information about You as ZaPaFlY, in its sole discretion, believes necessary or appropriate to comply with properly authorized civil, criminal or regulatory investigations or subpoenas or summons� issued by governmental authorities.
  3. HOW COMPANY PROTECTS YOUR INFORMATION.
    1. Confidentiality and Security  
When ZaPaFlY requests that You enter sensitive information, ZaPaFlY stores such information using secure procedures. ZaPaFlY also protects Your personal information off-line. Access to Your personal information is limited to employees who ZaPaFlY reasonably believes will need that information to provide services to You. However, ZaPaFlY is not responsible for the confidentiality, security or distribution of your own personal information by our partners and third parties outside the scope of our agreement with such partners and third parties.
    2. Links  
These sites may contain links to other sites. The linked sites are not necessarily under the control of ZaPaFlY. Please be aware that ZaPaFlY is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. ZaPaFlY encourages You to be aware when You leave these sites and to read the privacy policies of each and every websites that collects personally identifiable information. If You decide to access any of the third party sites linked to these sites, You do this entirely at your own risk. Any links to any partner of the Sites are the responsibility of the linking party, and ZaPaFlY shall not be responsible for notification of any change in name or location of any information on the Sites.
  4. CORRECTING INACCURACIES.
    1. Correcting/Updating Personal Information  
If personally identifiable information previously submitted to ZaPaFlY by You changes (such as name, e-mail address, telephone number, fax number, information about your interests in and use of various products, programs, and services, educational level and interests and/or billing information), You can update Your profile if you are a member at www.zapafly.com.
    2. Notification of Changes  
If ZaPaFlY decides to change the Privacy Policy for these sites, ZaPaFlY will post those changes on www.ZaPaFlY.com privacy policy section. All changes are effective immediately upon posting.
    3. Sites and Service Updates  
As necessary, ZaPaFlY may send You Site and service announcement updates. You are not able to un-subscribe from service announcements, which contain important information about the Sites. ZaPaFlY communicates via e-mail with You to provide requested services and to resolve issues relating to Your accounts.
    4. Consent to This Policy  
By using these sites, you consent to the collection and use of information by ZaPaFlY as specified in this Privacy Policy.

Privacy Policy Effective Date: December 12, 2006

Copyright � 2006 ZaPaFlY, LLC All rights reserved.
